# Adam Eckert Game Designer

Austin, TX (512)740-0278 adameckert3141@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/adam-eckert/

Recently graduated Game Designer with experience designing and documenting shipped games in a collaborative Agile environment of 20+ people. Strong communication and attention to detail with a passion for accessibility and an eye for striking, efficient design.

## Experience

## Coding with Kids

Coding academy with K-12 coding classes

Coding Instructor (Apr 2022 - Present)

- -Leading online classes of 1-8 students
- -Video editing for company recruitment material

## Heatwave Studios

Student-led organization at ASU

Design Lead (May 2019 - May 2021)

- -Developed standards for design documentation
- -Trained new members to use Unity
- -Designed main concepts and gameplay loops

Design Producer (Jan 2019 - May 2019)

- -Allocated tasks among designers
- -Aided collaboration between teams

Designer (Aug 2017 - May 2019)

- -Designed main game mechanics
- -Playtested and implemented gameplay tweaks
- -Built levels in Unity

# Skills

#### <u>Languages,</u> Engines, and IDEs

- -GML/GameMaker
- -HTML/CSS/JS
- -Python
- -C#
- -Java
- -Visual Studio/VSCode
- -Unity

#### Miscellaneous

- -Game Documentation
- -GitHub
- -Image/video editing

## Soft Skills

- -Communication
- -Critical thinking
- -Teamwork
- -Attention to detail
- -Adaptability
- -Problem solving

# Education

## <u>Arizona State University, Tempe AZ</u>

B.S. Informatics Certificate in Computer Gaming Cumulative GPA: 3.92 Honors: Summa Cum Laude, Dean's List (7 semesters)

## Relevant Coursework:

Programming (GML/Java/C#/JS), 3D Modeling and Animation, Game Engine Development, Databases, User Testing, Interface Design, Game Design Analysis

# Selected Projects

## Dodger

Solo Project GameMaker Studio 2 Personal project Arcadey bullet-hell Released on Itch.io Portfolio page

#### Color Phase

Designer Unity Heatwave Studios project 3D puzzle platformer Released on Steam <u>Portfolio page</u>

## Space Bubby

Project Lead GameMaker Studio 2 Academic project Top-down boss rush Released on Itch.io <u>Portfolio page</u>

To see my full portfolio with project write-ups, visit my website at adameckert.github.io